<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Fuzzy Logic ]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Explorable Explanations.]]></description><link>https://YakinRubaiat.github.io</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 09:55:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://YakinRubaiat.github.io/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[My Own Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>Hello My blog</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://YakinRubaiat.github.io/2019/02/01/My-Own-Blog.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://YakinRubaiat.github.io/2019/02/01/My-Own-Blog.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Yakin Rubaiat]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Test Post]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>Hello This is a test post again.klllllllk
.[1] The storm tracked parallel to the coast of Cuba before veering northward and crossing the Florida Keys, where it intensified into Tropical Storm Marco about 35 mi (55 km) south-southeast of Key West, Florida.[2]</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Tropical Storm Marco at peak intensity straddling the west coast of Florida on October 11
After passing midway between Key West and the Dry Tortugas, Tropical Storm Marco adopted a steady northward track and quickly intensified, reaching peak winds of 65 mph (100 km/h) on October 11, while still southwest of Englewood, Florida. The center of the storm continued on its off-shore parallel for another six hours after reaching its peak intensity, until it reached a position about six mi (10 km) west of Bradenton Beach; although the center of the storm remained offshore, much of its circulation was over land.[2] Initially the storm still was forecast to move ashore between Fort Myers and Sarasota.[4] However, the cyclone continued its northward trajectory, the center remaining offshore, and it weakened to a tropical depression prior to making landfall near Cedar Key early on October 12.[2][5]</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>After landfall, the cyclone accelerated in forward speed northward, weakening in intensity, and, by 1200 UTC on October 12, Marco became an extra-tropical cyclone. It turned to the northeast and east through South Carolina, following behind Hurricane Lili to its northeast.[3] For a time, the system&#8217;s proximity to Lili resulted in hints of the Fujiwhara effect, in which two tropical cyclone appear to rotate around each other.[6] The cold front that absorbed the weakening low was to the storm&#8217;s north on October 13,[2] though moisture from the remnants of Marco dropped heavy rainfall across the southeast United States for another day.[3]</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://YakinRubaiat.github.io/2019/02/01/A-Test-Post.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://YakinRubaiat.github.io/2019/02/01/A-Test-Post.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Yakin Rubaiat]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>